<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IIT NSTU</string>
    <string name="welcomeString">Institute of Information Technology (IIT), <b>Noakhali Science and Technology University</b> established in <b>2015</b> is an
        educational institution aimed at evolving high and IT professionals and qualified humanistic source in the realm of information technology.
        By assuring professionalism,distinction and recognition IIT ensures that alumni from our Institute can efficiently contribute to the IT industry
        of Bangladesh and all over the world.</string>
    <string name="md_auhidur_rahman">Md. Auhidur Rahman</string>
    <string name="assistant_professor_director_acting_"><![CDATA[ASSISTANT PROFESSOR & DIRECTOR (ACTING)]]></string>
    <string name="teachers">Teachers</string>
    <string name="this_is_an_imageview">this_is_an_imageview</string>
    <string name="DirectorMessage">It is my pleasure to introduce you to one of the vibrant Technological institutes in Bangladesh.  Institute of Information Technology (IIT), Noakhali Science and Technology University.

The Institute of Information Technology (IIT) has been established under Noakhali Science and Technology University Act 2001 section 41; as a constituent Institute with a separate Board of Governors.

The major objectives of the Institute of Information Technology (IIT) is to set-up a model of Education which can produce best-in-class human resources in IT and harnessing the multidimensional facets of IT in various domains. The Institute will evolve into a world-class academic institution with the highest quality of Education and Research facilities.

Established in the year of 2015, the “Newness” factor of IIT- NSTU and its close collaboration with other Institutions. IIT allows us to be constantly dynamic in our curriculum. We enjoy the flexibility to quickly respond to these rapidly changing global socio-economic conditions and can efficiently adapt the best practices of leading the Technical Institute. We consider this agility for Technical Education.

I look forward, the Institute of Information Technology (IIT).\n\n\n

Mr. Md. Auhidur Rahman\n

Assistant Professor and Director (Acting)\n

Institute of Information Technology (IIT)</string>
    <string name="assistant_professor_director_acting"><![CDATA[ASSISTANT PROFESSOR & DIRECTOR (ACTING)]]></string>
    >
</resources>
